The Beach House Murders is a thriller, tv movie film directed by Doug Campbell.
Novelist Sarah becomes a prime suspect in a homicide after a one-night tryst
with a mysterious stranger who turns up dead at her summer home.
Tony, played by Cj Hammond.
Miles, played by Devante Winfrey.
Sarah, played by Brittney Dorey.
Alice, played by Ashli Auguillard.
Jack, played by Kyle Williams.
Officer Evans, played by Carolyn Zanelli.
The Gilgo Beach serial killings were part of a series of murders on
Long Island, New York, spanning from 1993 to 2011.
Many of the victims' remains were found over a period of months in late 2010 and 2011 during a police search of the area
along Ocean Parkway, a road near the remote beach town of Gilgo in southern Suffolk County, New York.
In December 2010, the remains of four victims – Melissa Barthelemy, Maureen Brainard-Barnes, Megan Waterman, and Amber Lynn
Costello;  designated "The Gilgo Four" – were found within a quarter of a mile of each other near Gilgo Beach.
Six more sets of remains, believed to predate those four,  were found
in March and April 2011 in Suffolk and Nassau counties.
Not all of the victims are believed by police to
have been murdered by the same person.
The original search was prompted by the May 2010
disappearance of Shannan Gilbert in Oak Beach.
Like most of the later identified victims, Gilbert engaged
in sex work and advertised on Craigslist.
Her remains were found approximately 9 miles (14 km) northeast of where the ten
sets of remains had been found, but her cause of death is disputed.
Between July 2023 and December 2024, Rex Heuermann, a Manhattan-based architect and resident of Massapequa Park, Long Island, was charged with seven of
the Gilgo Beach murders, including those of the Gilgo Four as well as the murders of Sandra Costilla, Valerie Mack, and Jessica Taylor.
The tone is intense.